# Leonidas Leontidis

70C Greenwood Rd, E81NE, London, UK

DoB: 25/10/1993

Phone-Number: +44 78 321 699 68 E-mail: leonidas.leontidis@gmail.com

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/leonidas-leontidis

**Profile** 

Ambitious to succeed with a focus on achieving superb results and goals

Advanced relevant educational and professional experience

Advanced quantitative skills in conducting feasibility studies, performing research & recording data

Acute knowledge and understanding of various energy related business practices

Effective under pressure with the ability to meet tight deadlines

## Work Experience

#### Kallanish Index Services Limited (KIS)

12/2021-present

#### Position: Price Analyst

- Development and preparation of price indices and other market data for selected commodities
- Research, analysis and report preparation

#### AVINOIL S.A. - Motor Oil Group

10/2018-03/2020

#### Position: Fuel Pricing Coordinator | Operations & Customer Support

- Fuel Pricing Management
- Geolocation targeting pricing
- Management Reporting (Internal/External relationships)
- Optimization and Pricing Strategies
- Perform daily validation activities of relevant price information, accordingly to the company procedures
- PNL reporting and monitoring
- Perform checks on un-authorized moves and monitoring of mandates/limits
- Collaborate with IT and other departments for further developments
- Compliance with all internal and external regulation
- Audit readiness compliance
- Automation assistance for quicker implementations and changes

#### Position: Administrator Loyalty Program | Marketing

- Market Price Integrity
- ATL | BTL
- Client Complain Management

#### ASE-Engineering Services S.A.

10/2014-03/2015

#### Position: Survey & Geoconsulting Engineer | Trainee

- Verification for the accuracy of survey data, including measurements and calculations conducted at survey sites
- Preparation or supervision of the preparation of all data, charts, plots, maps, records, and documents related to surveys
- Calculation of heights, depths, relative positions, property lines, and other characteristics of terrain

#### Security and Surveillance Systems

06/2014-09/2014

#### Position: Technical Support and Installation

- Installation / service of commercial systems
- Programming of various commercial systems

#### Education

# **Brunel University London**

09/2020-09/2021

#### MSc Finance & Investment

(1 Year Course) - GPA: 2:1

Dissertation: "What is the effect of liquidity over the capital and stock market crisis, and how can it be restricted?"

"Advantages and Disadvatages in managing liquidity Crisis"

# Technical University of Crete (TUC) Chania, Crete, Greece

09/2011-06/2018

### MEng/(Diploma) (Hons) in Mineral Resources Engineering

(5 Years Course) - GPA: 2.1

# American College of Greece - Pierce

College - Athens, Greece 09/2008-06/2011

# Greek Apolytirion (17.2/20)

# Seminars / Conferences

# Seminars 6th National Conference of the Financial Engineering and Banking Society (FEBS) - University of Piraeus, Piraeus/ Greece

## Online Courses Certificates

# Bloomberg Market Concepts (BMC) - Bloomberg (November 18, 2020) Principles of Valuation: Time Value of Money – University of Michigan (April 12, 2016) - Coursera

### Other Skills

IT Skills

Languages

VBA, R, Matlab, Python, Microsoft Office, Excel Solver, Eclipse BIRT, AutoCAD

Greek Native

English Fluently C2 | ECCE and FCE 12/2007, Proficiency ECPE 03/2009

German Fluently **B1**Mandarin Beginner **A2** 

# Other Activities Sport Activities

Swimming, Soccer, Chess, Waterskiing, Alpine skiing, Tennis, Volleyball